{
  "uniqueId": "JLPT N5",
  "name": "JLPT N5 Reading Quiz",
  "article": "a",
  "instructions": "Type the reading of the below word in Hiragana!",
  "questionCreationStrategy": "IMAGE",
  "dictionaryLinkStrategy": "JISHO_QUESTION_WORD",
  "answerTimeLimitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "cardPreprocessingStrategy": "NONE",
  "discordFinalAnswerListElementStrategy": "QUESTION_AND_ANSWER_LINK_QUESTION",
  "scoreAnswerStrategy": "ONE_ANSWER_ONE_POINT",
  "additionalAnswerWaitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "discordIntermediateAnswerListElementStrategy": "CORRECT_ANSWERS",
  "answerCompareStrategy": "CONVERT_KANA",
  "compileImages": true,
  "cards": [
    {"question":"駅","answer":["えき"],"meaning":"station"},
    {"meaning":"afterwards","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"後","answer":["あと","ご","のち"]},
    {"meaning":"rain","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"雨","answer":["あめ"]},
    {"meaning":"to go","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"行く","answer":["いく","ゆく"]},
    {"meaning":"one","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"一","answer":["いち"]},
    {"meaning":"first of the month","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"一日","answer":["いちにち","ついたち"]},
    {"meaning":"five days, fifth day","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"五日","answer":["いつか"]},
    {"meaning":"five","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"五つ","answer":["いつつ"]},
    {"meaning":"now","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"今","answer":["いま"]},
    {"meaning":"to put in","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"入れる","answer":["いれる"]},
    {"meaning":"on top of","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"上","answer":["うえ","かみ","じょう"]},
    {"meaning":"behind","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"後ろ","answer":["うしろ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be born","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"生まれる","answer":["うまれる"]},
    {"meaning":"big","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"大きい","answer":["おおきい"]},
    {"meaning":"big","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"大きな","answer":["おおきな"]},
    {"meaning":"(honorable) mother","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"お母さん","answer":["おかあさん"]},
    {"meaning":"money","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"お金","answer":["おかね"]},
    {"meaning":"(honorable) father","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"お父さん","answer":["おとうさん"]},
    {"meaning":"Man","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"男","answer":["おとこ"]},
    {"meaning":"Boy","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"男の子","answer":["おとこのこ"]},
    {"meaning":"Adult","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"大人","answer":["おとな"]},
    {"meaning":"Woman","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"女","answer":["おんな"]},
    {"meaning":"Girl","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"女の子","answer":["おんなのこ"]},
    {"meaning":"foreign country","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"外国","answer":["がいこく"]},
    {"meaning":"Foreigner","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"外国人","answer":["がいこくじん"]},
    {"meaning":"to write","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"書く","answer":["かく"]},
    {"meaning":"Student","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"学生","answer":["がくせい"]},
    {"meaning":"School","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"学校","answer":["がっこう"]},
    {"meaning":"River","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"川","answer":["かわ"]},
    {"meaning":"tree, wood","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"木","answer":["き"]},
    {"meaning":"to hear, to listen to, to ask","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"聞く","answer":["きく"]},
    {"meaning":"North","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"北","answer":["きた"]},
    {"meaning":"Nine","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"九","answer":["きゅう","く"]},
    {"meaning":"Today","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"今日","answer":["きょう"]},
    {"meaning":"Country","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"国","answer":["くに"]},
    {"meaning":"to come","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"来る","answer":["くる","きたる"]},
    {"meaning":"car, vehicle","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"車","answer":["くるま"]},
    {"meaning":"Five","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"五","answer":["ご"]},
    {"meaning":"afternoon","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"午後","answer":["ごご"]},
    {"meaning":"nine days, ninth day","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"九日","answer":["ここのか"]},
    {"meaning":"Nine","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"九つ","answer":["ここのつ"]},
    {"meaning":"morning","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"午前","answer":["ごぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"this year","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"今年","answer":["ことし"]},
    {"meaning":"this month","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"今月","answer":["こんげつ"]},
    {"meaning":"the future, previous","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"先","answer":["さき"]},
    {"meaning":"year after next","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"さ来年","answer":["さらいねん"]},
    {"meaning":"Three","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"三","answer":["さん"]},
    {"meaning":"Four","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"四","answer":["し","よん"]},
    {"meaning":"Time","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"時間","answer":["じかん"]},
    {"meaning":"Below","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"下","answer":["した","げ","しも"]},
    {"meaning":"Seven","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"七","answer":["しち","なな"]},
    {"meaning":"Ten","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"十","answer":["じゅう","とお"]},
    {"meaning":"White","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"白","answer":["しろ"]},
    {"meaning":"White","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"白い","answer":["しろい"]},
    {"meaning":"Thousand","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"千","answer":["せん"]},
    {"meaning":"last month","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"先月","answer":["せんげつ"]},
    {"meaning":"teacher, doctor","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"先生","answer":["せんせい"]},
    {"meaning":"Outside","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"外","answer":["そと","ほか"]},
    {"meaning":"university","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"大学","answer":["だいがく"]},
    {"meaning":"tall, expensive","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"高い","answer":["たかい"]},
    {"meaning":"to put out","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"出す","answer":["だす"]},
    {"meaning":"to eat","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"食べる","answer":["たべる"]},
    {"meaning":"little","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"小さい","answer":["ちいさい"]},
    {"meaning":"little","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"小さな","answer":["ちいさな"]},
    {"meaning":"to go out","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"出かける","answer":["でかける"]},
    {"meaning":"to appear, to leave","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"出る","answer":["でる"]},
    {"meaning":"weather","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"天気","answer":["てんき"]},
    {"meaning":"electricity, electric light","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"電気","answer":["でんき"]},
    {"meaning":"electric train","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"電車","answer":["でんしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"telephone","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"電話","answer":["でんわ"]},
    {"meaning":"ten days, the tenth day","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"十日","answer":["とおか"]},
    {"meaning":"sometimes","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"時々","answer":["ときどき"]},
    {"meaning":"year","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"年","answer":["とし","ねん"]},
    {"meaning":"middle","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"中","answer":["なか","ちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"long","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"長い","answer":["ながい"]},
    {"meaning":"seven","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"七つ","answer":["ななつ"]},
    {"meaning":"seven days, the seventh day","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"七日","answer":["なのか"]},
    {"meaning":"name","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"名前","answer":["なまえ"]},
    {"meaning":"what","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"何","answer":["なん","なに"]},
    {"meaning":"two","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"二","answer":["に"]},
    {"meaning":"west","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"西","answer":["にし"]},
    {"meaning":"to enter, to contain","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"入る","answer":["はいる","いる"]},
    {"meaning":"eight","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"八","answer":["はち"]},
    {"meaning":"twenty days, twentieth","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"二十日","answer":["はつか"]},
    {"meaning":"talk, story","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"話","answer":["はなし"]},
    {"meaning":"to speak","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"話す","answer":["はなす"]},
    {"meaning":"half","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"半","answer":["はん"]},
    {"meaning":"east","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"東","answer":["ひがし","あずま"]},
    {"meaning":"left hand side","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"左","answer":["ひだり"]},
    {"meaning":"person","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"人","answer":["ひと"]},
    {"meaning":"one","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"一つ","answer":["ひとつ"]},
    {"meaning":"one month, January","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"一月","answer":["ひとつき","いちがつ"]},
    {"meaning":"one person","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"一人","answer":["ひとり"]},
    {"meaning":"hundred","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"百","answer":["ひゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"two","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"二つ","answer":["ふたつ"]},
    {"meaning":"two people","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"二人","answer":["ふたり"]},
    {"meaning":"two days, second day of the month","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"二日","answer":["ふつか"]},
    {"meaning":"book","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"本","answer":["ほん"]},
    {"question":"飲む","answer":["のむ"],"meaning":"to drink; to gulp; to swallow; to take (medicine), to smoke (tobacco), to engulf; to overwhelm, to keep down; to suppress, to accept (e.g. demand, condition), to make light of; to conceal"},
    {"meaning":"every day","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"毎日","answer":["まいにち"]},
    {"question":"飲み物","answer":["のみもの"],"meaning":"drink; beverage"},
    {"meaning":"before","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"前","answer":["まえ"]},
    {"question":"食べ物","answer":["たべもの"],"meaning":"food"},
    {"meaning":"ten thousand","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"万","answer":["まん"]},
    {"meaning":"right side","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"右","answer":["みぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"water","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"水","answer":["みず"]},
    {"meaning":"to show","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"見せる","answer":["みせる"]},
    {"meaning":"three days, third day of the month","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"三日","answer":["みっか"]},
    {"meaning":"three","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"三つ","answer":["みっつ"]},
    {"meaning":"south","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"南","answer":["みなみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to see, to watch","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"見る","answer":["みる"]},
    {"meaning":"six days, sixth day of the month","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"六日","answer":["むいか"]},
    {"meaning":"six","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"六つ","answer":["むっつ"]},
    {"meaning":"rest, holiday","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"休み","answer":["やすみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to rest","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"休む","answer":["やすむ"]},
    {"meaning":"eight","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"八つ","answer":["やっつ"]},
    {"meaning":"mountain","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"山","answer":["やま"]},
    {"meaning":"eight days, eighth day of the month","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"八日","answer":["ようか"]},
    {"meaning":"four days, fouth day of the month","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"四日","answer":["よっか"]},
    {"meaning":"four","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"四つ","answer":["よっつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to read","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"読む","answer":["よむ"]},
    {"meaning":"next month","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"来月","answer":["らいげつ"]},
    {"meaning":"next year","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"来年","answer":["らいねん"]},
    {"meaning":"six","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"六","answer":["ろく"]},
    {"question":"お兄さん","answer":["おにいさん"],"meaning":"older brother; elder brother, (vocative) young man; buddy; fella; laddie"},
    {"question":"お姉さん","answer":["おねえさん"],"meaning":"elder sister, (vocative) young lady, miss (referring to a waitress, etc.), ma'am (used by geisha to refer to their superiors), older girl (no relation)"},
    {"question":"お手洗い","answer":["おてあらい"],"meaning":"toilet; restroom; lavatory; bathroom"},
    {"question":"お茶","answer":["おちゃ"],"meaning":"tea (usu. green), tea break (at work), tea ceremony"},
    {"question":"風","answer":["かぜ","ふう"],"meaning":"wind; breeze; draught; draft, manner; behaviour; behavior, cold; influenza, method; manner; way; style, appearance; air, tendency, folk song (genre of the Shi Jing), wind (one of the five elements)"},
    {"question":"乗る","answer":["のる"],"meaning":"to get on (train, plane, bus, ship, etc.); to get in; to board; to take; to embark, to get on (e.g. a footstool); to step on; to jump on; to sit on; to mount, to reach; to go over; to pass, to follow; to stay (on track); to go with (the times, etc.), to take part; to participate; to join, to get into the swing (and sing, dance, etc.), to be deceived; to be taken in, to be carried; to be spread; to be scattered, to stick; to attach; to take; to go on"},
    {"question":"仕事","answer":["しごと"],"meaning":"work; job; business; occupation; employment; vocation; task, work"},
    {"question":"雪","answer":["ゆき"],"meaning":"snow"},
    {"question":"元気","answer":["げんき"],"meaning":"lively; full of spirit; energetic; vigorous; vital; spirited, healthy; well; fit; in good health"},
    {"question":"兄","answer":["あに"],"meaning":"elder brother; older brother"},
    {"question":"冬","answer":["ふゆ"],"meaning":"winter"},
    {"question":"初めて","answer":["はじめて"],"meaning":"for the first time, only after ... is it ...; only when ... do you ..."},
    {"question":"友達","answer":["ともだち"],"meaning":"friend; companion"},
    {"question":"取る","answer":["とる"],"meaning":"to take; to pick up; to harvest; to earn; to win; to choose, to steal, to eat; to have (a meal), to remove (one's glasses, etc.), to compete (in sumo, cards, etc.); to play"},
    {"question":"口","answer":["くち"],"meaning":"mouth, opening; hole; gap; orifice, mouth (of a bottle); spout; nozzle; mouthpiece, gate; door; entrance; exit, speaking; speech; talk (i.e. gossip), taste; palate, mouth (to feed), opening (i.e. vacancy); available position, invitation; summons, kind; sort; type, opening (i.e. beginning), counter for mouthfuls, shares (of money), and swords, mouth; speech, counter for people or implements"},
    {"question":"難しい","answer":["むずかしい"],"meaning":"difficult; hard; troublesome; complicated; serious (disease, problem, etc.), fussy; particular; fastidious; hard to please; displeased, gloomy; glum; sullen; serious (look), dirty; unclean; filthy; detestable, unpleasant; uncomfortable; creepy; spooky"},
    {"question":"土曜日","answer":["どようび"],"meaning":"Saturday"},
    {"question":"売る","answer":["うる"],"meaning":"to sell"},
    {"question":"夏","answer":["なつ"],"meaning":"summer"},
    {"question":"閉まる","answer":["しまる"],"meaning":"to be shut; to close; to be closed, to be locked, to tighten; to be tightened, to become sober; to become tense"},
    {"question":"好き","answer":["すき"],"meaning":"liking; fondness; love"},
    {"question":"妹","answer":["いもうと"],"meaning":"younger sister, darling (only of a woman); dear; honey; my betrothed, one's sister, friend"},
    {"question":"金曜日","answer":["きんようび"],"meaning":"Friday"},
    {"question":"部屋","answer":["へや"],"meaning":"room; chamber, apartment; flat; pad, stable"},
    {"question":"子","answer":["こ"],"meaning":"child, young (animal), young woman; young geisha, offshoot, interest, new shares, player who is not a dealer (in cards, mahjong, etc.)"},
    {"question":"安い","answer":["やすい"],"meaning":"cheap; inexpensive, calm; peaceful; quiet"},
    {"question":"家","answer":["いえ","うち"],"meaning":"house; residence; dwelling, family; household, lineage; family name, house; home (one's own), (one's) family; (one's) household"},
    {"question":"寒い","answer":["さむい"],"meaning":"cold (e.g. weather), uninteresting (esp. joke); lame; dull; weak; corny"},
    {"question":"少し","answer":["すこし"],"meaning":"small quantity; little; few; something, little while, short distance"},
    {"question":"遠い","answer":["とおい"],"meaning":"far; distant"},
    {"question":"帰る","answer":["かえる"],"meaning":"to return; to come home; to go home; to go back, to leave, to get home; to get to home plate"},
    {"question":"店","answer":["みせ"],"meaning":"store; shop; establishment; restaurant"},
    {"question":"道","answer":["みち"],"meaning":"road; street; way; path; course; route; lane, distance; ways (e.g. \"a long ways\"), the way (of proper conduct, etc.); one's way; morals, teachings (esp. Confucian or Buddhist); dogma, field (of medicine, etc.); subject, way; method; means"},
    {"question":"忘れる","answer":["わすれる"],"meaning":"to forget; to leave carelessly; to be forgetful of; to forget about; to forget (an article)"},
    {"question":"忙しい","answer":["いそがしい"],"meaning":"busy; occupied; hectic, restless; hurried; fidgety"},
    {"question":"遅い","answer":["おそい"],"meaning":"slow, late (e.g. \"late at night\"), too late, dull; stupid"},
    {"question":"手","answer":["て"],"meaning":"hand; arm, forepaw; foreleg, handle, hand; worker; help, trouble; care; effort, means; way; trick; move; technique; workmanship, hand; handwriting, kind; type; sort, one's hands; one's possession, ability to cope, hand (of cards), direction, move (in go, shogi, etc.)"},
    {"question":"走る","answer":["はしる"],"meaning":"to run, to travel (movement of vehicles); to drive, to hurry to, to retreat (from battle); to take flight, to run away from home, to elope, to tend heavily toward, to flash; to streak; to shoot through (e.g. pain)"},
    {"question":"赤ちゃん","answer":["あかちゃん"],"meaning":"baby; infant"},
    {"question":"買う","answer":["かう"],"meaning":"to buy; to purchase, to value; to have a high opinion, to stir; to provoke"},
    {"question":"日曜日","answer":["にちようび"],"meaning":"Sunday"},
    {"question":"言葉","answer":["ことば"],"meaning":"language; dialect, word; words; phrase; term; expression; remark, speech; (manner of) speaking"},
    {"question":"映画","answer":["えいが"],"meaning":"movie; film"},
    {"question":"春","answer":["はる"],"meaning":"spring; springtime, New Year, prime (of one's life, etc.), adolescence; puberty, sexuality"},
    {"question":"時","answer":["とき"],"meaning":"time; hour; moment, occasion; case, chance; opportunity; season, the times; the age; the day, tense"},
    {"question":"月","answer":["つき","げつ"],"meaning":"moon, month, month (of the year); used after number or question word (e.g. nan or nani), Monday"},
    {"question":"言う","answer":["いう","ゆう"],"meaning":"to say; to utter; to declare, to name; to call, to go (e.g. \"the alarm went ping\"); to make a noise"},
    {"question":"木曜日","answer":["もくようび"],"meaning":"Thursday"},
    {"question":"覚える","answer":["おぼえる"],"meaning":"to memorize; to memorise; to commit to memory; to learn by heart; to bear in mind; to remember, to learn; to pick up; to acquire, to feel, to think; to regard"},
    {"question":"見える","answer":["みえる"],"meaning":"to be seen; to be in sight, to look; to seem; to appear, to come, to have an audience; to meet; to see, to face (an enemy); to confront, to serve (esp. as one's wife)"},
    {"question":"歌","answer":["うた"],"meaning":"song, classical Japanese poetry (esp. tanka), modern poetry"},
    {"question":"歌う","answer":["うたう"],"meaning":"to sing, to sing (one's praises in a poem, etc.); to compose a poem; to recite a poem"},
    {"question":"止まる","answer":["とまる"],"meaning":"to stop (moving); to come to a stop, to stop (doing, working, being supplied); to come to a halt; to cease; to be stopped; to be suspended, to alight; to perch on, to remain; to abide; to stay (in the one place), to be limited to; to be confined to, to cease; to stop; to be over"},
    {"question":"歩く","answer":["あるく"],"meaning":"to walk"},
    {"question":"英語","answer":["えいご"],"meaning":"English (language)"},
    {"question":"母","answer":["はは"],"meaning":"mother"},
    {"question":"水曜日","answer":["すいようび"],"meaning":"Wednesday"},
    {"question":"洗う","answer":["あらう"],"meaning":"to wash; to cleanse; to rinse, to inquire into; investigate, to purify (one's heart), to lave (e.g. shore); to wash over (e.g. deck); to sweep"},
    {"question":"海","answer":["うみ"],"meaning":"sea; ocean; waters"},
    {"question":"消える","answer":["きえる"],"meaning":"to go out; to vanish; to disappear"},
    {"question":"消す","answer":["けす"],"meaning":"to erase; to delete; to cross out, to turn off power, to extinguish; to put out, to bump off"},
    {"question":"肉","answer":["にく"],"meaning":"flesh, meat, the physical body (as opposed to the spirit), thickness, ink pad"},
    {"question":"火曜日","answer":["かようび"],"meaning":"Tuesday"},
    {"question":"父","answer":["ちち"],"meaning":"father"},
    {"question":"犬","answer":["いぬ"],"meaning":"dog (Canis (lupus) familiaris), snoop (i.e. a detective, a spy, etc.), loser; asshole, counterfeit; inferior; useless; wasteful"},
    {"question":"猫","answer":["ねこ"],"meaning":"cat, shamisen, geisha, wheelbarrow, clay bed-warmer, bottom; submissive partner of a homosexual relationship, cat"},
    {"question":"生きる","answer":["いきる"],"meaning":"to live; to exist, to make a living; to subsist, to be in effect; to be in use; to function, to come to life; to be enlivened, to be safe (in baseball, go, etc.)"},
    {"question":"生徒","answer":["せいと"],"meaning":"pupil"},
    {"question":"目","answer":["め","もく"],"meaning":"eye; eyeball, eyesight; sight; vision, look; stare; glance, an experience, viewpoint, stitch; texture; weave, ordinal number suffix, somewhat; -ish, order, item (of a budget revision, etc.), counter for go pieces; counter for surrounded positions (in go)"},
    {"question":"耳","answer":["みみ"],"meaning":"ear, hearing, edge; crust, selvedge (non-fray machined edge of fabrics); selvage"},
    {"question":"私","answer":["わたし","わたくし"],"meaning":"I; me"},
    {"question":"答える","answer":["こたえる"],"meaning":"to answer; to reply"},
    {"question":"窓","answer":["まど"],"meaning":"window"}
  ]
}